{
    "subject": "resource/All_American_Chump",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of All American Chump is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8880510926246643,
            "question": "Is English a common language for films like 'All American Chump'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8034223318099976,
            "question": "Does the film 'All American Chump' feature any other languages besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7677775025367737,
            "question": "What language is the film 'All American Chump' spoken in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7383555769920349,
            "question": "Is 'All American Chump' a film with dialogue in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6955731511116028,
            "question": "What language is primarily used in the movie 'All American Chump'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6912837624549866,
            "question": "If you wanted to watch 'All American Chump', would you need to understand English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6274886727333069,
            "question": "Would someone who doesn't speak English be able to understand 'All American Chump'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5976519584655762,
            "question": "Can you tell me if 'All American Chump' was made with subtitles for other languages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17584004998207092,
            "question": "Are there many English-language movies produced in America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03518659621477127,
            "question": "What is the dominant language used in Hollywood films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of All American Chump is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5981_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there many English-language movies produced in America?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5981_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me if 'All American Chump' was made with subtitles for other languages?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5981_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would someone who doesn't speak English be able to understand 'All American Chump'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5981_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5981_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe context documents mention that \"chump\" is an informal term for a person easily fooled, and also refer to a short, thick piece of wood. Later on, it is mentioned that Tyson's promoter, Don King, referred to Joe Clark's payment as \"chump change\", which implies that the amount was insignificant. This context suggests that English is indeed the language in which the term \"All American Chump\" would be used, and that its meaning is related to being a dupe or easily fooled person."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided supports that the term \"chump\" is used in English, and definitions and usages related to it are given. This aligns with the query stating that the language of \"All American Chump\" is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}